<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DICE IT</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DICE IT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 13:27:57 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Neovim Format on Save - No Plugin</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/neovim-format-on-save-no-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 13:27:57 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/neovim-format-on-save-no-plugin/</guid>
      <description>Now that null-ls is no longer going to be maintained, I was wondering how to get the same behavior, but without null-ls.
So my end goal is this:
I want to execute format on a specific file whenever I save that file. Specifically I want to run the elixir formatter whenever I save an *.ex or *.exs file And the solution is:
vim.api.nvim_create_autocmd(&amp;#34;BufWritePre&amp;#34;, { group = vim.api.nvim_create_augroup(&amp;#34;FormatBeforeSaveElixirFiles&amp;#34;, {clear = true}), pattern = {&amp;#34;*.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Day Top Interview 150</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blog/first-day-top-interview-150/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 14:54:23 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blog/first-day-top-interview-150/</guid>
      <description>Contents Exercise Description Code With Me Exercise Setup Solution 1 Solution 2 Solution 3 Today is the first day of my journey with my friend Dennis Dang on doing the Top 150 Interview Study Plan from Leet Code Exercise Description The first exercise is about Merge Sorted Array . The description is:
You are given two integer arrays nums1 and nums2, sorted in non-decreasing order, and two integers m and n, representing the number of elements in nums1 and nums2 respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DICE IT - Software Consultancy</title>
      <link>http://example.org/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 05:43:27 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/about/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Dice IT LLC, your trusted partner in software consultancy and development! Led by Eduardo Borsa, an experienced software engineer with 8 years of expertise, we are a cutting-edge company specializing in Elixir development.
Are you passionate about software development and eager to stay ahead of the curve in this ever-evolving field? Look no further! The DICE IT Blog is your go-to resource for cutting-edge insights, expert opinions, and practical tips related to software development, with a particular focus on Elixir.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
